airsassociation.org 2019-12-30

# Privacy Policy - Association of Internet Research Specialists | AIRS

## Privacy Policy

  1. __
  2. [Home](https://www.airsassociation.org/)
  3. Privacy Policy

### **Privacy Policy Statement

* * *

**

We are committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy applies to all the web pages related to this website. All the information gathered in the online forums on the website is used to personally identify users that subscribe to this service. The information will not be used for anything other than which is stated in the _Terms & Conditions _of use for this service. None of the information will be sold or made available to anyone.

The Site may collect certain information about your visit, such as the name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the Site; the pages that you access while at the Site and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. This information is used to help improve the Site, analyze trends, and administer the Site.

We may need to change this policy from time to time in order to address new issues and reflect changes on our site. We will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose that information to anyone. Please refer back to this policy regularly. If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please send us an E-mail.

By using this website, you signify your acceptance of our _Privacy Policy_. If you do not agree with this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of the website following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.

### **Cookie/Tracking Technology

* * *

**

The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

**Third-Party Links**

In an attempt to provide increased value to our Users, we may provide links to other websites or resources. You acknowledge and agree that we are not responsible for the availability of such external sites or resources, and do not endorse and are not responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for the privacy practices or the content (including misrepresentative or defamatory content) of such websites, including (without limitation) any advertising, products or other materials or services on or available from such websites or resources, nor for any damage, loss or offence caused or alleged to be caused by, or in connection with, the use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on such external sites or resources.

#### 

Association of Internet Research Specialists is the world's leading community for the Internet Research Specialist and provide a Unified Platform that delivers, Education, Training and Certification for Online Research.

### Follow Us on Social Media
